[
  {
    "question": "「風」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "かぜ",
    "choices": [
      "ふう",
      "かぜ",
      "はやて",
      "せんぷう"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「花」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "はな",
    "choices": [
      "はな",
      "か",
      "ばな",
      "かおり"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「春」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "はる",
    "choices": [
      "はる",
      "あき",
      "ふゆ",
      "なつ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「海」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "うみ",
    "choices": [
      "うみ",
      "かわ",
      "みず",
      "たに"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「夜」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "よる",
    "choices": [
      "ひる",
      "よる",
      "あさ",
      "ゆう"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「赤」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "あか",
    "choices": [
      "あか",
      "あお",
      "しろ",
      "くろ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「手」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "て",
    "choices": [
      "て",
      "あし",
      "みみ",
      "め"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「牛」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "うし",
    "choices": [
      "うま",
      "うし",
      "ぶた",
      "ひつじ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「空」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "そら",
    "choices": [
      "かわ",
      "くも",
      "そら",
      "やま"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「星」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "ほし",
    "choices": [
      "ほし",
      "つき",
      "ひ",
      "みず"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「山」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "やま",
    "choices": [
      "かわ",
      "やま",
      "もり",
      "そら"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「雨」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "あめ",
    "choices": [
      "あめ",
      "ゆき",
      "かぜ",
      "ひ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「母」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "はは",
    "choices": [
      "はは",
      "ちち",
      "あね",
      "おば"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「火」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "ひ",
    "choices": [
      "みず",
      "ひ",
      "つち",
      "かぜ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「友」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "とも",
    "choices": [
      "いえ",
      "とも",
      "あい",
      "はな"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「川」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "かわ",
    "choices": [
      "うみ",
      "そら",
      "かわ",
      "やま"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「白」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "しろ",
    "choices": [
      "くろ",
      "あお",
      "あか",
      "しろ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「本」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "ほん",
    "choices": [
      "ほん",
      "もと",
      "やま",
      "かわ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「水」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "みず",
    "choices": [
      "みず",
      "ひ",
      "あめ",
      "かわ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "「子」はどう読む？",
    "correct": "こ",
    "choices": [
      "こ",
      "いぬ",
      "ねこ",
      "あさ"
    ]
  }
]
